[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To whom did the inventor of the typewriter sell his patent?", "correct_answer": "A maker of guns", "incorrect_answers": ["A sewing machine company", "Thomas A. Edison", "The US government"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During World War II, no Axis troops landed on any of the 48 American states.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Star Wars character commanded the first Death Star?", "correct_answer": "Grand Moff Tarkin", "incorrect_answers": ["Darth Vader", "Colonel Veers", "The Emperor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor voiced Moses and God in the 1998 animated blockbuster movie The Prince of Egypt?", "correct_answer": "Val Kilmer", "incorrect_answers": ["Danny Glover", "Steve Martin", "Ralph Fiennes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For what is Scottish Sir James Dewar famous?", "correct_answer": "Inventing the vacuum flask.", "incorrect_answers": ["Writng the screenplay to The 39 Steps.", "Standardizing the method to produce Scotch whiskey.", "Exporting the first Scotch whiskey to the USA."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The newton (N), named after Sir Isaac Newton in recognition of his work on classical mechanics, is a unit measuring what?", "correct_answer": "Force", "incorrect_answers": ["Mass", "Speed", "Weight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin A plays an important role in vision, growth, healthy skin and hair, immune function, and reproduction. Which of these is not a significant source of Vitamin A?", "correct_answer": "Nuts and grains", "incorrect_answers": ["Egg yolks", "Dark leafy greens", "Sweet potatoes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2004, this famous show business family became the second clan to have three generations of Oscar winners.", "correct_answer": "The Coppolas", "incorrect_answers": ["The Douglases", "The Howards", "The Weavers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This word is used to denote a group of cobras.", "correct_answer": "Quiver", "incorrect_answers": ["Sedge", "Knot", "Bale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a traditional dish in Austria and Germany made of a thin peace of veal meat coated with flour, egg and bread crumb.", "correct_answer": "Wiener Schnitzel", "incorrect_answers": ["Currywurst", "Stollen", "Spanferkel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors did not appear in Woody Allens 1977 comedy movie Annie Hall?", "correct_answer": "Jack Nicholson", "incorrect_answers": ["Diane Keaton", "Woody Allen", "Sigourney Weaver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The national motto of what island country is Ever Conscious of God We Aspire, Build and Advance as One People?", "correct_answer": "Grenada", "incorrect_answers": ["New Zealand", "Papua New Guinea", "Micronesia"]}]